Inventory of the Donald S. Rothchild papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Research materials, 1960-2006
  - Military performance, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 39: 3)
  - MIlitary coups and rule, 1982-2000 (Box-folder 39: 4)
  - Military intervention: East Africa, 1964-1999 (Box-folder 39: 5)
  - Ujamma village policy, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 39: 6)
  - Goals and choices: development strategies, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 39: 7)
  - Political repercussions of economic malaise, 2000 (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Political responses to scarcity, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 39: 9)
  - Agriculture in Kenya, 1980 (Box-folder 39: 10)
  - Durable peace after civil war, 1995 (Box-folder 39: 11)
  - Reconfiguring state-ethnic relations, 1993 (Box-folder 39: 12)
  - Papers of U Thant, 1976 (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Congo Republic, 1960-1972 (Box-folder 40: 2-3)
  - Oscar Schaecter, legal analysis of the Congo, 1965 (Box-folder 40: 4)
  - United States and Congo mediation, 1961-1992 (Box-folder 40: 5)
  - United States and Katanga, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 40: 6)
  - United Nations peacekeeping in the Congo, 1966 (Box-folder 40: 7)
  - Congo crisis, 1990 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - Congo, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 41: 2)
  - Congo, 1962 (Box-folder 41: 3-4)
  - United States and Katanga, 1962 (Box-folder 41: 5)
  - Congo federalism, 1960 (Box-folder 41: 6)
  - Shaba, 1978 (Box-folder 41: 7)
  - Congo crisis, 1992 (Box-folder 41: 8)
  - The United Nations in the Congo, 1962 (Box-folder 41: 9)
  - United Nations documents on the Congo, 1960-1988 (Box-folder 41: 10)
  - Zaire, 1978 (Box-folder 41: 11)
  - United States and Congo: Eisenhower period, 1993 (Box-folder 41: 12)
  - United States and Katanga, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 42: 1-4)
  - United Nations in the Congo, 1962 (Box-folder 42: 5)
  - Congo-Lyndon B. Johnson Library, 1964-1990 (Box-folder 42: 6)
  - Congo, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 42: 7)
  - Congo-John F. Kennedy Library, 1962 (Box-folder 42: 8)
  - United States and ethnicity: Congo integrity (Box-folder 42: 9)
  - Zaire-federalism, 1969 (Box-folder 42: 11)
  - Congo-separatism, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 43: 1-2)
  - Congo Republic, 1960 (Box-folder 43: 3-4)
  - Congo-John F. Kennedy lIbrary, 1962 (Box-folder 43: 5)
  - ONUC's civilian operations, 1964 (Box-folder 43: 6)
  - Congo, 1998 (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Katangism, 1961 (Box-folder 44: 2)
  - Congo-KInshasa, 1997 (Box-folder 44: 3)
  - Zaire civil war, 1997 (Box-folder 44: 4-5)
  - Congo-John F. Kennedy Library, 1961 (Box-folder 44: 6-7)
  - United States and Katanga, 1962 (Box-folder 45: 1)
  - Biafra, 1970 (Box-folder 45: 2)
  - Biafran War-Richard Nixon, 1969-1989 (Box-folder 45: 3)
  - Self-determination: Biafra/United States, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 45: 4)
  - Organization of African Unity mediation: Biafra, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 45: 5)
  - United States and Biafra, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 45: 6)
  - Biafran War-observer teams, 1968 (Box-folder 45: 7)
  - Nigeria-Biafra mediation, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 45: 8)
  - Charles R. Nixon, "Self-Determination: The Nigeria/Biafra Case", 1972 (Box-folder 45: 9)
  - Biafra: Quakers, 1968-1985 (Box-folder 45: 10)
  - Tanzania: recognition of Biafra, 1968 (Box-folder 45: 11)
  - Nigerian/Biafran crisis, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 46: 1-2)
  - Chibuike Uche, "Money Matters in a War Economy: The Biafran Experience", 2002 (Box-folder 46: 3)
  - Private mediation-Biafra/Sudan, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 46: 4)
  - Biafran War-U.S. attitudes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 46: 5)
  - United States and Biafra, 1978 (Box-folder 46: 6)
  - Magnanimity and Nigerian civil war, 1967-1987 (Box-folder 46: 7)
  - Nigerian civil war, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Rwanda, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 47: 2-4)
  - Arusha accords, 1993 (Box-folder 47: 5)
  - Nigeria-Gerald Ford Library, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 47: 6)
  - Post-civil war Nigeria-marginalization of Ibos, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - Rwanda tribunal, 1994 (Box-folder 48: 2)
  - Lebanon (1958): Dulles phone calls (Box-folder 48: 3-7)
  - Lebanon (1958): special assistants (Box-folder 48: 8)
  - Lebanon (1958): correspondence (Box-folder 48: 9)
  - Ann Whitman file, 195 8 (Box-folder 49: 1)
  - Lebanon (1958): OCB series (Box-folder 49: 2)
  - Lebanon (1958): Special assistants (Box-folder 49: 3-4)
  - Lebanon (1958): Briefing notes (Box-folder 49: 5)
  - Lebanon (1958): Dulles phone calls (Box-folder 49: 6-7)
  - Lebanon (1958): Dulles file (Box-folder 49: 8)
  - Lebanese consociationalism: 1943-1975, 1965-1987 (Box-folder 49: 9)
  - Externally imposed peace: Lebanon, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 49: 10)
  - Lebanon (1958): White House memos (Box-folder 50: 1-2)
  - Lebanon (1958): Special assistants (Box-folder 50: 3-4)
  - Lebanon (1958): NSC policy papers (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - United States and Lebanon, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 50: 6)
  - Lebanon-Gerald Ford Library, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 50: 7)
  - Macedonia/Albania, 2001 (Box-folder 50: 8)
  - Lebanon-Gerald Ford Library, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 50: 9)
  - Bosnia, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 51: 1)
  - Biafra documents, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 51: 2)
  - East AFrican federation, 1983 (Box-folder 51: 3)
  - Private mediation, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 51: 4)
  - Organization of African Unity mediation and Biafra, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 51: 5)
  - Biafra War-Jennifer Ramos, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 51: 6)
  - Cordier papers, 1961 (Box-folder 51: 7)
  - Lebanon, 1964-1999 (Box-folder 52: 1-2)
  - Russia/Chechnya, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 52: 3)
  - Kosovo agreement, 2001 (Box-folder 52: 4)
  - Bosnia, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 52: 5-6)
  - Miscellaneous articles relating to American foreign policy, 1984-1997 (Box-folder 53: 1-3)
  - Bosnia, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 53: 4-5)
  - Lebanese civil war, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 53: 6)
  - Lebanon, 1975-1994 (Box-folder 53: 7-8)
  - Serbia/Bosnia/Kosovo, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 53: 9)
  - Africa, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - Africa, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - Miscellaneous articles relating to American foreign policy, 1983-2002 (Box-folder 54: 2-3)
  - Miscellaneous articles relating to African economic conditions and politics, 1984 (Box-folder 54: 4)
  - Third World Quarterly, 1981 (Box-folder 54: 5)
  - World Development Report, 1997 (Box-folder 54: 6)
  - Africa's Adjustment and Growth in the 1980s, 1989 (Box-folder 54: 7)
  - African Alternative Framework fo Structural Adjustment Programmes for Socio-Economic Recovery and Transformation, 1988 (Box-folder 54: 8)
  - National Security Study Memorandum, 1969 (Box-folder 54: 9)
  - Miscellaneous articles relating to economic and social conditions in Africa, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Theoretical perspectives in political science, 1969-1990 (Box-folder 55: 2-4)
  - Reports on economic development, 1984-2004 (Box-folder 55: 5-9)
  - State and policy process, 1980 (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - Discussion outline, 2000 (Box-folder 56: 2)
  - Syllabi and course materials, 1996-2006 (Box-folder 56: 3-4)
  - Miscellaneous articles relating to concepts in political science, 1978-2006 (Box-folder 56: 5-6)
  - World Bank publications, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 56: 7-11)
  - Miscellaneous publications, 1994 (Box-folder 56: 12-13)
- Administrative file, 2004-2006
  - Teaching evaluations, 2004-2006
    - 2004 (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - 2005 (Box-folder 57: 2-3)
    - 2006 (Box-folder 57: 4-5)
- Research materials, 1966-2006
  - Organization of African Unity-Lagos plan of action for the economic development of Africa, 1980 (Box-folder 57: 6)
  - International debt crisis, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 57: 7)
  - Bosnia, 1983 (Box-folder 57: 8)
  - Political culture and U.S. foreign policy, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 57: 9)
  - Demand processes, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 57: 10-11)
  - Miscellaneous articles relating to Africa and the international debt crisis, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 57: 12)
  - Course materials, 1978-1990 (Box-folder 58: 1-2)
  - Concepts of ethnicity and class, 1990-2002 (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - Causes of conflict, 2000 (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - Patterns of conflict, 1970-1991 (Box-folder 58: 5)
  - Polilcies on nation-state relations, 2000 (Box-folder 58: 6)
  - "Ethnic and Racial Conflict: From Bargaining to Violence", 2000 (Box-folder 58: 7)
  - U.S. and conflict management, 1992 (Box-folder 58: 8)
  - Mechanisms of conflict management, 1990 (Box-folder 58: 9)
  - Transitions to democracy, 2005 (Box-folder 58: 10)
  - Polyarchical regimes, 2005 (Box-folder 58: 11)
  - Comparative public policy, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 58: 12-13)
  - Relative deprivation, 1985 (Box-folder 58: 14)
  - Dimensions of choice, 1985 (Box-folder 58: 15)
  - Ghana, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 59: 1-2)
  - Problems of government, 1970 (Box-folder 59: 3)
- Administrative file, 1980-2006
  - Poliltical Science 134, final examination, 1996 (Box-folder 59: 4)
  - Political Science 2, final examination, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 59: 5)
  - Comparative politics field exam reading list, 1994 (Box-folder 59: 6)
  - Political Science 126, midterm and final examinations, 1981-2004 (Box-folder 59: 7-8)
- Research materials, 1960-1990
  - Dayton peace accord, 1995 (Box-folder 60: 1)
  - Bosnia, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 60: 2)
  - Britain and European integration, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 60: 3)
  - Ghana's economic crisis and policy options, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 60: 4)
  - Great Britain: Immigration issue, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 60: 5)
  - Voting systems, 1980 (Box-folder 60: 6)
  - France, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 60: 7)
  - Neo-colonialism and Africa, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Soviet security and external relations, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 61: 2)
  - Soviet federalism and nationalities issue, 1986 (Box-folder 61: 3)
  - Soviet political culture, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 61: 4)
  - Soviet poltical system, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 61: 5)
  - Soviet Communist Party, 1964-1981 (Box-folder 61: 6)
  - Soviet hegemony: system functions, 1981 (Box-folder 61: 7)
  - Soviet control methods, 1982 (Box-folder 61: 8)
  - Soviet constitution and rights of citizens, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 61: 9)
  - Soviet economy, 1987 (Box-folder 61: 10)
  - Hegemony and resource allocation, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 61: 11)
  - Authoritarian systems, 1980 (Box-folder 61: 12)
  - State building: Soviet perceptions, 1980 (Box-folder 61: 13)
  - Ghana: return to civilian rule, 1980 (Box-folder 61: 14)
  - Single-party systems: Ghana, 1978 (Box-folder 61: 15)
  - African military coups, 1981 (Box-folder 61: 16)
  - Nigeria, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 62: 1)
  - Nigeria, 1970-1982 (Box-folder 62: 2)
  - Nigerian constitution, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 62: 3)
  - Nigeria, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 62: 4)
  - Nigeria-party politics, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 62: 5)
  - Religious activism in Nigeria, 1981-2004 (Box-folder 62: 6)
  - Pollicies and principles of colonial powers, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 62: 7)
  - Single-party systems and economic development, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 62: 8)
  - Nationalism, 1970 (Box-folder 62: 9)
  - Imperialism, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 62: 10)
  - Nationalism, 1997 (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Nigeria, 1968-1980 (Box-folder 63: 2)
  - Nicaragua-Miskitos negotiations, 1986 (Box-folder 63: 3)
  - U.S. and New Guinea, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 63: 4)
  - Mauritania, 1979-1994 (Box-folder 63: 5)
  - Mauritius, 1966-1995 (Box-folder 63: 6)
  - Nagorno-Karabakh, 2001 (Box-folder 63: 7)
  - Malawi; racial minorities, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 63: 8)
  - Malaysia, 1961-1989 (Box-folder 63: 9)
  - Malaysia: ethnicity, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 63: 10)
  - Mali, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 63: 11)
  - Nigeria: federalism, 1960-1978 (Box-folder 64: 1-3)
  - Nigeria: federal elections, 1959 (Box-folder 64: 4)
  - Nigeria: indigenization, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 64: 5)
  - Nigeria, 1955-2002 (Box-folder 64: 6-7)
  - Nigeria, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 65: 1-3)
  - Nigeria: federalism, 1964-1979 (Box-folder 65: 4)
  - Nigerian coup and after, 1966-1987 (Box-folder 65: 5)
  - Senegambia, 1960-1989 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - International Peace Academy, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 66: 2)
  - African unity and the O.A.U., 1968-1995 (Box-folder 66: 3)
  - U.N./O.A.U. and conflict resolution, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 66: 4)
  - World bank and ethnicity, 1992 (Box-folder 66: 5)
  - Organization of African Unity and conflict resolution, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 66: 6-7)
  - Nigeria, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 66: 8)
  - East Africa, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 67: 1)
  - Federation: French Africa, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 67: 2)
  - French colonialism, 1953-1960 (Box-folder 67: 3)
  - Finance and federalism, 1965 (Box-folder 67: 4)
  - Ghana/Guinea/Mali union, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 67: 5)
  - Latin American integration, 1953-1969 (Box-folder 67: 6)
  - Malil Federation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67: 7)
  - Pan-Africanism, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 67: 8)
  - Senegal River, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 67: 9)
  - Seminar on federal problems, 1961-1972 (Box-folder 68: 1)
  - Federalism and economic development, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 68: 2)
  - Federal experiments and African politics, 1966 (Box-folder 68: 3)
  - Swiss federalism, 1967 (Box-folder 68: 4)
  - Central African market, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 68: 5)
  - External aids to regional integration, 1967 (Box-folder 68: 6)
  - African federations and the diplomacy of decolonization, 1968 (Box-folder 68: 7)
  - Political communities, 1980 (Box-folder 68: 8)
  - Types of poltical communities: confederation, 1967 (Box-folder 68: 9)
  - Types of political communities: federal states, 1975 (Box-folder 68: 10)
  - Types of political communities: unitary states, 1975 (Box-folder 68: 11)
  - Types of poltical communities: leagues, 1975 (Box-folder 68: 12)
  - Nationalism and unification, 1980 (Box-folder 68: 13)
  - Advantages of federation, 1980 (Box-folder 68: 14)
  - German federalism, 1975 (Box-folder 68: 15)
  - Types of political communities: international organizations, 1980 (Box-folder 68: 16)
  - Types of political communities: common markets, 1966 (Box-folder 68: 17)
  - Types of political communities: military multi-lateral, 1966 (Box-folder 68: 18)
  - Dynamics of federal integration, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 68: 19)
  - Arab federations, 1957-1973 (Box-folder 68: 20)
  - Economic Community of West African States, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 68: 21)
  - Congo-John F. Kennedy Library, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69: 1-4)
  - U.S. anti-self-determination: Philippines, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 69: 5)
  - Zambian mediation: Kenya-Somali conflict, 1975 (Box-folder 69: 6)
  - O.A.U. mediation: Ethiopia-Somalia, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 69: 7)
  - O.A.U mediation: Western Sahara, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 69: 8)
  - O.A.U. buffering: Chad, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 69: 10)
  - O.A.U. pressure and non-pressure, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 69: 11)
  - African state mediations, 1980 (Box-folder 69: 12)
  - U.N. as mediator in ethnic conflicts, 1992 (Box-folder 69: 13)
  - African Charter on Human and Peoples' Rights, 1981 (Box-folder 69: 14)
  - Economic Community of West African States, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 69: 15)
  - U.N. and the Congo, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 70: 1)
  - U.S. and Katanga: John F. Kennedy Library, 1962 (Box-folder 70: 2)
  - Congo: John F. Kennedy Library, 1962 (Box-folder 70: 3)
  - Cordier papers, 1961 (Box-folder 70: 4)
  - Congo: colonial period, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 70: 5)
  - Congo, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 70: 6)
  - U.N. peacekeeping in the Congo, 1966 (Box-folder 70: 7)
  - Congo miscellaneous, 1968-1993 (Box-folder 71: 1)
  - Investing in Leverage: O.A.U., regional peacekeeping, Africa crisis response force, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 71: 2)
  - Fundamental law concerning the structure of the Congo, 1960 (Box-folder 71: 3)
  - Biafra, 1968 (Box-folder 71: 4-5)
  - Germany, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 71: 6)
- Administrative file, 2004
  - Teaching evaluations, 2004 (Box-folder 71: 7-8)
- Research materials, 1957-2006
  - Congo: John F. Kennedy Library, 1962 (Box-folder 72: 1-3)
  - Congo: Lyndon B. Johnson Library, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 72: 4-5)
  - Crisis in the Congo, 1965 (Box-folder 72: 6)
  - Congo Crisis: 1960-1963, 1966-1989 (Box-folder 72: 7)
  - Congo: John F. Kennedy Library, 1962 (Box-folder 73: 1-2)
  - U.S. and Katanga: John F. Kennedy Library, 1962 (Box-folder 73: 3-4)
  - Congo: Lyndon B. Johnson Library, 1964 (Box-folder 73: 5-6)
  - Zaire, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 73: 7)
  - Limits of self-determination, 1965 (Box-folder 73: 8)
  - Peacekeeping-Katanga, 1993 (Box-folder 73: 9)
  - Congo criisis, 1994 (Box-folder 73: 10)
  - Congo: John F. Kennedy Library, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 74: 1-2)
  - U.S. and Katanga: John F. Kennedy Library, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 74: 3-10)
  - Congo: Lyndon B. Johnson Library, 1964 (Box-folder 74: 11)
  - Zaire: Richardson mediation, 1997 (Box-folder 74: 12)
- Printed matter, 1960-2000
  - Ghana, 1970-1992
    - 1970 (Box-folder 75: 1)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 75: 2)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 75: 3)
  - Kenya, 1972-1975
    - 1972 (Box-folder 75: 4)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 75: 5)
  - Tanzania, 1976-1979
    - 1976 (Box-folder 75: 6)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 75: 7)
  - Uganda, 1957-1964
    - 1957 (Box-folder 75: 8)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 75: 9)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 75: 10)
  - Kenya, 1954-1974
    - 1954 (Box-folder 76: 1)
    - 1959 (Box-folder 76: 2)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 76: 3)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 76: 4)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 76: 5-6)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 76: 7-8)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 76: 9-17)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 76: 18-23)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 76: 24-28)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 76: 29-30)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 76: 31)
  - Ghana, 1970-1982
    - 1970 (Box-folder 76: 32)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 76: 33)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 76: 34)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 76: 35)
  - Nigeria, 1962-1972
    - 1962 (Box-folder 76: 36)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 76: 37-38)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 76: 39)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 76: 40)
  - Uganda, 1971-1993
    - 1971 (Box-folder 76: 41)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 76: 42)
  - Tanzania, 1965
    - 1965 (Box-folder 76: 43)
  - Rhodesia, 1959
    - 1959 (Box-folder 76: 44)
  - Kenya, 1953-1992
    - 1953 (Box-folder 77: 1)
    - 1954 (Box-folder 77: 2)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 77: 3)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 77: 4-9)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 77: 10-14)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 77: 15-17)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 77: 18-20)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 77: 21)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 77: 22)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 77: 23-24)
  - Ghana, 1988
    - 1988 (Box-folder 78: 1)
  - Uganda, 1965-1968
    - 1965 (Box-folder 78: 2)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 78: 3)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 78: 4)
  - Kenya, 1962-1982
    - 1962 (Box-folder 78: 5)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 78: 6)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 78: 7-8)
- Research materials, 1960-1964
  - Allen W. Dulles papers, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 78: 9)
- Printed matter, 1959-1990
  - East Africa, 1980
    - 1980 (Box-folder 79: 1)
  - Ghana, 1978-1988
    - 1978 (Box-folder 79: 2)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 79: 3-4)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 79: 5-6)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 79: 7)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 79: 8-9)
  - Uganda, 1959-1969
    - 1959 (Box-folder 79: 10-11)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 79: 12)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 79: 13)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 79: 14)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 79: 15)
  - Kenya, 1968-1986
    - 1968 (Box-folder 79: 16)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 79: 17)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 79: 18)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 79: 19)
  - Nigeria, 1963-1970
    - 1963 (Box-folder 80: 1)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 80: 2-5)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 80: 6)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 80: 7-8)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 80: 9-10)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 80: 11)
  - Kenya, 1954-1970
    - 1954 (Box-folder 80: 12-13)
    - 1956 (Box-folder 80: 14)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 80: 15)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 80: 16)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 80: 17)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 80: 18)
  - Ghana, 1964-1968
    - 1968 (Box-folder 80: 19-20)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 80: 21)
  - Uganda, 1966
    - 1966 (Box-folder 80: 22)
- Research materials, 1938-1983
  - Kenya: transfer of power and land, 1938-1969 (Box-folder 81: 1)
  - Demands for state creation, group autonomy, and enhancement, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 81: 2)
  - Ghana-report and financial statement, 1976 (Box-folder 81: 3)
  - Nigeria: miscellaneous, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 81: 4)
  - Confederation, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 81: 5)
  - Nigeria: separate states issue, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 81: 6-7)
  - Nigerian minorities, 1956-1967 (Box-folder 81: 8)
- Printed matter, 1962-1968
  - Kenya, 1962-1968
    - 1962 (Box-folder 81: 8)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 81: 9-10)
  - Africa-General, 1967
    - 1967 (Box-folder 82: 1)
  - Nigeria, 1967-1971
    - 1967 (Box-folder 82: 2)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 82: 3-4)
  - Kenya, 1969-1973
    - 1969 (Box-folder 82: 5)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 82: 6-8)
  - Ghana, 1967-2001
    - 1967 (Box-folder 82: 7)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 82: 8)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 82: 9-11)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 82: 12-15)
    - 2001 (Box-folder 82: 16)
- Research materials, 1975-1984
  - Nigerian states, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 82: 17)
  - Ethnicity and depoliticization, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 82: 18)
  - Kenya-Somalia, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 83: 1)
  - Congo: federalism, 1962-1987 (Box-folder 83: 2)
  - Majimbo, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 83: 3)
  - Italian regionalism, 1970 (Box-folder 83: 4)
  - Load factors, 1964 (Box-folder 83: 5)
  - Federalism: motivation, 1964 (Box-folder 83: 6)
  - Federalism: bibliography, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 83: 7)
  - Ghana: elections and regionalsim, 1960-1981 (Box-folder 83: 8)
  - Macedonina, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 83: 9-10)
  - Northern Ireland, 1969-1984 (Box-folder 84: 1-4)
  - Kurds, 1974-1994 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - Bargaining: Israel-Arabs, 1973-1995 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - Israel-Palestine accord, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 84: 6)
  - Northern Ireland, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 85: 1-7)
  - Israel, 1972-1997 (Box-folder 85: 8)
  - Pan-Africanism, 1959-1972 (Box-folder 86: 1)
  - Algeria, 1958-2004 (Box-folder 86: 2)
  - Federalism in West Africa, 1959-1962 (Box-folder 86: 3-4)
  - West Indian integration, 1956-1972 (Box-folder 86: 5)
  - Mitchell report, 1996 (Box-folder 86: 6)
  - Northern Ireland-implementation, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 86: 7)
  - Anglo-Irish agreement, 1985 (Box-folder 86: 8)
  - Northern Ireland agreement, 1998 (Box-folder 86: 9)
  - Southern African integration, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 86: 10)
  - Tanganyika-Zanzibar merger, 1964-1994 (Box-folder 86: 11)
  - Sri Lanka, 1990-2005 (Box-folder 87: 1-3)
  - Sri Lanka-Indian mediation, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 87: 4)
  - Sierra Leone, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 87: 5-8)
  - Nicaragua, 1988-1998 (Box-folder 87: 9)
  - Cambodia, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 87: 10-11)
  - Implementation: Namibia, 1999 (Box-folder 87: 12)
  - Altering bases of choice, 1971 (Box-folder 88: 1)
  - Nigeria: foreign polciy, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 88: 2)
  - Return of refugees, 1997 (Box-folder 88: 3)
  - Reputation in negotiations, 1998 (Box-folder 88: 4)
  - Northern Ireland agreement, 1998 (Box-folder 88: 5-6)
  - Managing arms: Mozambique, 1996 (Box-folder 88: 7)
  - Peace transition in Uganda, 1993 (Box-folder 88: 8)
  - El Salvador, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 88: 9)
  - Truth commission versus prosecution, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 88: 10)
  - Sierra Leone, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 88: 11-12)
  - Constitutional developments, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 89: 1)
  - Zambia, 1970 (Box-folder 89: 2-3)
  - Miscellaneous writings, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 69: 4)
  - Uganda: federation, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 69: 5)
  - Creation of states, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 69: 6)
  - Miscellaneous Africa, 1963-1980 (Box-folder 69: 7)
  - Ideology and national interest in Africa, 1964-1998 (Box-folder 90: 1)
  - America's cautious involvement in Africa's struggle, 1999 (Box-folder 90: 2)
  - Human rights, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 90: 3-5)
  - African Crisis Response Initiative (ACRI), 1997-2001 (Box-folder 90: 6-8)
  - Cartels, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 91: 1)
  - Basic human needs, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 91: 2)
  - Multinational corporations and Africa, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 91: 3)
  - Non-alignment, 1967-1983 (Box-folder 91: 4)
  - Realism versus idealism, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 91: 5)
  - Foreign aid, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 91: 6)